myfreeplr.com 2009-04-08

# MyFreePLR.com - Privacy Policy

## OUR PRIVACY POLICY

MyFreePLR.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time. 

In addition, online visitors who wish to purchase a membership through our Web site must provide their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. All credit card transactions occur over a secure connection. 

All online visitor data collected by MyFreePLR.com is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations. 

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. MyFreePLR.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer: 

  * Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc. 
  * Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. 
  * Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.

Check out the FTC's site for more tips on protecting children's privacy online. 

**Contacting Us  
**  
We can be reached by contacting: [MyFreePLR.com](http://www.chontichamarijne.com/contact)

* * *
